stuartwilde.com 2012-11-22

# Privacy Statement | Stuart Wilde | The Official Author Website

We appreciate your interest and your visit to this Web site. We respect your privacy and want you to feel comfortable visiting our sites. Any personal information provided by you will be held strictly confidential and will never be given to another party.

**Email Privacy Policy**  
We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.

**Why did you receive an email from us?**  
If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

**How we protect your privacy**  
We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.

**Sharing and Usage**  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

**How can you stop receiving email from us?**  
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email.
